Previously on Desperate Housewives
《绝望的主妇》  前情提要
Lynette went back to work. And Tom filled his days.
勒奈特又成了职业女性  汤姆的生活倍感充实
-You're good at this girl talk thing.
-你对女性的话题很擅长
Thanks
谢谢
Do you at least know why he steals?
那你知道他偷窃的原因吗
I steal to hurt you.
为了伤害你
Bree struggled to understand her husband's problem,
布里尽力理解丈夫的问题
While down the street,
而在街道另一边
Edie finally figured out her husband's plan.
伊迪终于弄清楚了她丈夫的计划
So you could get close to the man  who killed your family.
你跟我结婚就是为了  接近那个害死你家人的人
He was never punished.
他从未受任何惩罚
Rose kemper was a survivor.
瑞斯·凯普是位幸存者
You could see that by looking into her eyes.
从她眼神中就能看出端倪
She had buried one husband,
她亲自葬夫
Given birth to five children,
抚养5个孩子
Survived illness, bankruptcy,
经历过病痛  破产的折磨
Even the loss of her teeth...
甚至牙齿掉光的疼痛
As a result,
结果就是
Rose kemper was no longer afraid of anything.
瑞斯·凯普无所畏惧
Sadly, the man who climbed into her window that night
不幸的是  那晚爬进她窗户里的那个男人
Was unaware of this...
对此一无所知
But rose was more than happy to explain it to him.
但瑞斯很乐意给他点颜色瞧瞧
Get out of here! just get the hell out!
滚出去  快滚
I'm calling the police. do you hear me?!
我要给警察打电话  你听到吗
Mrs. kemper?
凯普夫人
Katherine! what are you doing here?
凯瑟琳  你来这做什么
Oh, i heard you weren't feeling well,
我听说你感觉不太好
So i brought you some flowers.
所以给你带了点花
The doctors tell me you had a mild heart attack.
医生说你心脏病险些复发
Did they tell you why?
他们告诉你原因了吗
It was death.
是死神
He came for me.
他来找我了
Death came for you?
死神去找你了
But i chased him out with my baseball bat.
但是我用棒球棍把他赶走了
I gave him a good whack, too, right on the old noggin.
而且我还狠狠打了他一顿  就在脑门上
How much morphine do they have you on?
他们给你注射了多少吗啡
You know that shelf where I keep my knickknacks?
我有个放摆设的架子
He tried to take one.
他想偷走
Death collects knickknacks.
死神也收集摆设
he couldn't get me, he went after that other lady--
他带不走我  就把另一个女人带走了
The one who crashed.
那个撞到电线杆的女人
Edie britt?
伊迪·布利特
Oh, yes, and i saw everything.
是她  我什么都看到了
Death just staggered out into the street,
死神摇摇晃晃走到街道上
And he raised his hands,
举起了手
And he made her run into that light pole.
让她撞到了电线杆上
Katherine...
凯瑟琳
You believe me, don't you?
你相信我说的话吧
Oh, i would never make anything like this up.
我从不说谎的
Know you wouldn't, sweetheart.
我相信你不会的
Listen, i'll stop by tomorrow.
我明天再来看你
You just get your rest, okay?
你先休息会儿  好吧
Uh, katherine?
凯瑟琳
If you see death lurking in the hall,
你如果看到死神藏在大厅里
You tell him he better not come around here,
告诉他不要到这边来
'cause i am not afraid of him.
因为我一点也不怕他
No, rose kemper was afraid of anything...
是的  瑞斯·凯普什么也不怕
But the man who had broken into her home...
但那个闯进她家的男人
Was now very afraid of rose kemper.
现在却很怕她
http://www.yyets.net/
人人影视字幕组  荣誉出品
校对:小门柴   压制:孤帆   时间轴:娅娅
翻译:鱼公主   小小天鱼   桃金娘银
The fact is everyone does it--
为了掩盖真相
Sometimes with the help of an overturned cushion...
人们有时把垫子翻过来
Sometimes by means of a large potted plant...
时而用大盆栽来遮蔽丑行
Other times using the top button of a shirt.
或者用衬衣上的扣子  来掩盖事实
Yes, everyone has something
是的  人人都会掩藏些事
They want to keep hidden from prying eyes...
不想让好打听的人知道
It's hard to believe you got this bump just by falling.
很难相信你这伤是摔倒弄的
But some people are better at cover-ups than others.
但一些人比别人更擅长于掩盖
I know, but that's what happened.
我知道  但就这么发生了
I went for a walk, i tripped,i hit head
我出去散步  被绊了一脚  然后就这样了
Okay, well, everything's looking much better.
恩  现在看起来好多了
I see no reason why he shouldn't be released this weekend.
这周末就可以出院了
Really? that soon?
真的吗  这么快
You can pick him up in the afternoon.
你可以下午来接他
Orson, i'll check in one more time before you go.
奥森  你出院前我再过来看一次
Well, you don't seem all that thrilled
你看起来
About the prospect of me coming home.
并不怎么期盼我回家
Honey, i don't mean to be negative.
亲爱的  我不是不想你回去
It's just...
只是
What's gonna happen?
还会发生什么事
Will you keep stealing and lying to me?
你还会继续偷东西对我撒谎吗
I love you, but i just can't put up with that anymore.
我爱你  但我实在受不了那些了
Don't worry. things are gonna be different.
别担心  一切都会不一样了
how? well, i've been doing a lot of thinking lately,
我最近想了很多
And i've decided... Finally, to be happy.
我终于  决定  要快乐起来
How can you just decide something like that?
你怎么能决定这种事情
Look...
听着
There are things that i don't like about my life,
我生命中有些东西是不喜欢的
But there is so much that is good.
但好的东西还是很多的
Do i really wanna risk losing everything?
我真的要冒险失去一切吗
I mean, if i can decide to be resentful and jealous,
我是说  如果我能决定愤怒和嫉妒的话
I can damn well decide to be happy...
我同样也能决定快乐
And be the kind of husband that you deserve.
成为你值得去爱的老公
Do you really mean that
你是说真的吗
I do.
真的
I hope so...because i just cannot take any more lying
希望如此  因为我再也受不了你撒谎了
You won't have to.
再也不会了
I can promise you that.
我可以向你保证
Dave?
大卫
Hello?
有人吗
Dave?
大卫
He didn't answer. okay, now i'm starting to get worried.
他不说话  现在我开始担心了
Yeah, i left that casserole three days ago,
我前几天把餐盘放那里了
And it's still there.
现在还在那
I'm surprised the squirrels haven't gotten to it.
好奇怪松鼠居然没吃掉
Maybe they did.
也许它们去了
Anybody seen any dead squirrels around here?
有人在周围看到死松鼠吗
even if dave wants to be alone
即使大卫想一个人待着
We have to make sure he's taken care of. we owe it to edie.
我们也要确保他好好的  我们欠伊迪的
I say we keep showing up here until he lets us help him
我们还是尽量让他接受我们的帮助
we need to be annoying and persistent.
我们要叽叽喳喳  坚持不懈
We're good at that.
我们对此比较擅长
so who can come by later and check on him?
那谁过会来看看他
I'd do it, but i'm working late.
我想来  但我要工作
I'm in the classroom all day
我一天都要在教室里待着
and i have meetings after.
之后还要开会
I have a rehearsal dinner to cater.
我要准备一套晚宴
ugh, and i have a garden clu meeting.
我有一个园艺俱乐部的聚会
You're in a garden club?
你参加园艺俱乐部了
Yeah, i just joined.
是的  刚加入的
Wait. there wouldn't happen to be actual gardeners
等等  不会真有园丁
In this club, would there?
在这个俱乐部吧
hot shirtless gardeners, great abs and learner's permits
有你穿这么劲爆的园丁吗  别人让你进吗
Gee, this bit just gets funnier and funnier.
真是越来越有趣了
Oh, we tease because we love.
我们这么逗你是因为我们喜欢
Now back to dave. i'll ask mike to check in on him.
说回到大卫  我会让迈克去看他
That'd be great.
那太好了
remember to tell him "annoying and persistent".
记得告诉他要"叽叽喳喳  坚持不懈"
And i can make another casserole.
我可以做另外一个餐盘
yeah, 'cause he hasn't suffered enough.
是啊  他受的还不够
That's a bit that i never get tired of.
这种调侃我最喜欢了
Dave? hello?
大卫  在吗
It's mike.
我是迈克
Dave?
大卫
Hey, i'm, uh, sorry to barge in.
抱歉直接闯进来
I just want to make sure you're okay.
只想确定你没事
Katherine made you lasagna.
凯瑟琳给你做了千层面
Thought i'd be a good idea to eat something.
感觉吃点东西会好点
Want me to get you a plate?
想让我给你拿个盘子吗
I'm good.
我很好
You'll get through this.
你要挺过去
Buddy, you will.
伙计  你会挺过去的
Look, i have gone through some really--
听着  我也经历过
You'noing.
你那什么都不是
And if you stand there
如果你还站在这里
and try to tell me you understand how I feel
试图给我说你能理解我的感受
I swear to god, i'm gonna lose my mind.
我发誓  我会发狂的
-I'm just trying to help.
-我只想帮帮你
you can't, okay?
你帮不了
So why don't you go back to katherine
那你为什么不去找凯瑟琳
And your happy little life and leave me the hell alone?
过你那快乐的小日子  让我一人静静
You're right.
你是对的
I don't have any idea what you're going through.
我不知道你都经历了什么
Sweetie, i'm home.
亲爱的  我回来了
Don't make plans on tuesday.
周二别有什么计划
We're having dinner at the solis' and...
我们要去索利斯家吃饭
What's that look on your face?
你怎么了
You didn't eat dairy again, did you?
没有再吃乳制品吧
No. i've been working out.
我一直在健身
If you're good, i'll let you cop a feel.
如果你喜欢  我让你摸下
that's okay. i can see it from here.
不用了  从这就可以看到
It's thrilling.
很棒
you smell good.
你真香
Mm. i just took a shower,
我刚洗了个澡
And i know where you're going with this... mm.
我知道你想干什么
-But i am exhausted.
-但我实在太累了
oh, come on, lynette. please?
勒奈特  拜托
Ooh. whining--that's hot.
发牢骚了  真火辣
Fine.
好吧
Let's have sex.
我们来嘿咻吧
But i warn you, i'm just gonna lie here,
但我警告你  我只是躺在这
Resenting the whole time, waiting for this hell to be over.
一直对你抱怨  等这该死的事情结束
Okay. if you're sure.
没问题  只要你肯
Tom!
汤姆
-Come on!
-别这样
all right, all right. okay, forget it.
好  好  不做了
Wait.
等等
You just took a shower? where?
你刚刚洗了澡  在哪
At work.
公司
Didn't know you had a shower there.
我不知道你那还有浴室
I don't. carlos does.
我没有  卡洛斯有
So you went into carlos' office,
那你去了卡洛斯的办公室
Stripped naked and took a shower?
直接脱光然后洗澡
No, i went into carlos' bathroom,
不是  我进了他的  浴室
Closed the door, then stripped naked and took a shower.
把门关上  然后脱光开始洗澡
I'm not comfortable with this. what if he walked in?
我听着不舒服  他要是进去怎么办
Then maybe i'd get that raise i've been asking for.
如果他要求的话  我可以考虑
This isn't funny.
我没跟你开玩笑
You already spend 16 hours a day with the guy,
你一天跟他相处16个小时
and now I found out some hours you are naked and wet.
有时还全身湿透  赤身裸体好几个小时
hours? it was two minutes.
好几个小时  两分钟而已
It's not like i'm lighting candles
又不是点着蜡烛
And putting on barry white.
听着巴里·怀特(北美男歌手)
I don't care. i want it to stop.
我不介意  我不喜欢这样
Fine.
行
I should've just had sex. i'd be asleep by now.
我应该刚刚给做了  现在好好睡觉
and, ladies, we have been asked by the city council
女士们  市议会要求我们
To beautify the center divider on main street.
美化主要街道的中央分禾器
So make sure your calendars are clear next tuesday.
所以要确定下周二没别的安排
I know i'm new here at the garden club,
我知道我在园丁俱乐部是新人
But what's with all the gardening?
但为什么干这些活
I thought this was just an excuse
我以为我们只是
To get together for bitchin' and boozin'.
聚在一起  发发牢骚  喝酒狂欢呢
blame Edna, the flower fascist.
要怪就怪爱德娜  那个花卉法西斯分子
Yeah, when we first joined,
我们刚加入时
We used to sit around in wicker chairs,
经常坐在柳椅上
Drinking margaritas and just looked at the flowers.
喝喝玛格丽特鸡尾酒  赏赏花
i'd killed from margarita
我爱死玛格丽特鸡尾酒了
Don't cluster, ladies. vary the colors.
女士们  不要聚在一起  颜色要分开
And she's the one i'd kill.
我也爱死她了
I mean,who is really in charge?
谁是这里真正的负责人
Alice Koontz. grand mal seizure while driving.
爱丽丝.库恩兹  开车时癫痫病发
Well, this edna has got to be stopped.
我们要阻止这个爱德娜
How?
怎么阻止
Oh, my god. you're planning a coup, aren you? i'm in.
天哪  你要罢工了是吧  我加入
Me, too.
我也加入
Well, that's three. who else can we get?
我们三个人了  还能找到谁
Definitely judy.
朱迪也会参加
And terry's allergic to everything.
泰瑞讨厌这一切
One bee sting, and she blows up like...
只要稍稍刺激她一下  她就会
Well, like, judy.
像朱迪一样  加入我们
How about the woman in the overalls?
那个穿工装裤的女人怎么样
Phyllis? she just got her second d.u.i.
菲里丝  她超喜欢喝酒
If there's cocktails, she's in.
如果有鸡尾酒的话  她肯定来
Okay, so the lush gives us six.
那我们现在6个人了
-What about them?
-她们呢
no way. they're all friends of edna's.
不行  她们都是爱德娜的朋友
Mm. all right, so they have six, and we have six.
好了  她们6个人  我们也是6个
We're gonna need a tiebreaker.
我们的决胜局开始了
Hey, uh, are men allowed to join the group?
男的也可以加入吗
I don't know why they wouldn't be.
我觉得可以
Ladies, start your blenders.
女士们  准备好你们的调酒器吧
Orson, I heard you wanted to see me.
奥森  听说你想见我
Yes, Dr. kagen.
是的  凯科医生
I heard you're treating a lady across the hall.
我听说  你是对面的那位女士的主治医生
-you mean Rose Kemper?
-你是说瑞斯·凯普吗
she's actually my neighbor.
是  她其实是我的邻居
I wanted to know how she's doing.
我想知道她怎么样
sorry. I can't discuss With anyone she's not related to.
抱歉  我不能和没有亲属关系的人谈论病人情况
Oh. well, that's a problem.
这是个问题
See, she has no family or friends, for that matter.
你看  她没有家人  也没有朋友
And, uh, because of her dementia...
而且  因为她痴呆了
Who said she has dementia?
谁说她痴呆了
Well, certainly you've heard some of her bizarre ramblings.
你肯定听过她说的一些不知所云的疯话
If she doesn't have dementia,
如果她没痴呆
It's something just as troubling.
同样还是让人担忧
She has been saying some very disturbing things.
她一直在说令人不安的话
But I wasn't aware it was an ongoing situation.
但我不觉得这是个大问题
Oh, yes, it is.
不  这是个大问题
And I'm so worried about her going back to that big house
我很担心  她回到她的大房子后
With no one to look after her.
没人照顾她
Hmm. i hate to get social services involved.
我不喜欢社会服务部门牵扯进来
They'd probably just stick her in some state-run facility.
他们可能会把她接进国立的疗养院
Oh, that would be a shame.
真遗憾啊
But what if she ends up hurting herself or someone else?
但如果她最后误伤自己或其他人呢
I mean, i am no lawyer,
我又不是律师
But wouldn't the hospital be liable?
难道医院不应该负责任吗
Hey, Penny. aren't you gonna be late for school?
你好  佩妮  你上学是不是晚了
My stupid brothers hid my homework. real mature.
我那些白痴哥哥把我的作业给藏起来了  长不大的家伙
Is your mom ready?
你妈妈准备好了吗
She's in the shower.
她正在冲澡
What?
什么
Lynette!
勒奈特
Carlos, you're early!
卡洛斯  你早了
Didn't you get my text? the meeting got moved up.
你没收到我的短信吗  会议提前了
Oh, crap. i'll be right there!
该死  我这就下去
Lynette, you okay?
勒奈特  你没事吧
Lynette?
勒奈特
Are you all right?
你还好吧
If you don't answer me, i'm coming in there.
如果你不出声  我就要进去了
Oh, my god.
天哪
All right, doctor. thank you. bye.
好的  医生  谢谢  再见
He says that since you weren't out very long,
他说  因为你失去知觉的时间不长
You should be fine. And don't worry about the meeting.
应该没什么大碍  你也不用担心会议
I pushed it to lunch, and I can handle it alone.
我把它推迟到午饭了  我可以自己处理
no, I'm fine. I wanna go
不  我没事  我可以去
You sure?
你确定吗
Okay, I'll let you get dressed.
好  等你穿上衣服
Hey, carlos, quick question for ya.
卡洛斯  一个小问题
Last thing I remember, I was in the shower, naked,
我只记得  我在洗澡  没穿衣服
Reaching for the soap.
我去捡肥皂
Then i was here on the bed, under a blanket...
然后我就在床上了  盖着毯子
Still naked.
还是没穿衣服
And my question is,
我想问
How did I get from there to here?
我是怎么从那边到这边的
I carried you.
我把你抬过来的
which means you saw me...
这就是说  你看到我
Lynette, the only thing i was thinking about
勒奈特  我当时只想
Was were you gonna be all right?
你会不会出事
Oh, well, I appreciate that.
好  真的谢谢你
And here's something else I'd appreciate--
如果咱们对这件事情守口如瓶
Could we not tell anyone else about this?
我会更感激你
Not tell anyone? I'm a first-time hero.
不告诉任何人吗  我可是第一次当英雄
This would be my lead item in this year's chrismas letter
这可是我今年圣诞节吹嘘的主要事迹
If tom finds out, he'll freak.
如果汤姆知道的话  他可能要发疯了
He has this weird thing
他总有些奇怪的想法
About being the only guy who gets to see me naked.
他觉得他应该是唯一能看到我的裸体的人
You got it. now get dressed. we gotta go.
好  我不会说  穿上衣服咱们走吧
Could you maybe step outside?
你能不能到外面等我
I only do one show a day.
我一天只展示一次
Here you go!
来了
Edna, here's your diet soda.
爱德娜  这是你的无糖可乐
Try to keep your pants on.
希望你一直保持身材
You know, I don't mean to be a killjoy,
我不想泼冷水
But are we gonna do any planting today?
今天我们会去种花草吗
There's some seeds in this. Knock yourse out.
这里面有些种子  请随便吧
Patty, do you mind if I steal tom for a sec?
帕蒂  你不介意我把汤姆借走一秒钟吧
Okay, but only a sec.
好  就一秒哦
What's up?
怎么了
First of all, you're a real prince for coming today.
首先  你真是好人  今天来帮我们
Thanks to you, our coup is complete.
由于你  我们的政变成功了
No problem.
不用谢
Anyway, I know you must be bored silly,
我知道你肯定无聊死了
So go ahead and make your escape.
你可以走  去吧
Actually, i'm thinking of staying.
事实上  我想留下来
I'm having a great time, meeting some nice people.
我过得很愉快  和大家聊得很开心
Yeah, about that-- I gotta warn you.
关于这点  我得警告你
Patty's kinda got a thing for married men.
帕蒂总是喜欢勾搭已婚男人
Oh, patty? No! No, no. She's just being nice.
帕蒂  不会吧  她只是人很好
Yes, she's like that. She'll give you the bra off her back.
不  她喜欢这样  她什么都愿意给你
We're just talkin'.
我们只是在聊天
"oh, tom, what big arms you have"--
哦  汤姆  你的胳膊真壮啊
That kind of talkin'?
这种聊天吗
Oh, that. Okay, fine.
这个  好吧
Fine. Point taken.
好了  知道啦  听你的
Okay, great. Now if you'll excuse me,
好  现在  如果你不介意
I have to get back to my gardening.
我要继续"种花"了
So Orson's decided to be happy.
所以奥森决定要快乐
Isn't that great?
这不是很好吗
He sounded very sincere.
他听起来很诚恳
I'll bet.
我相信
So just how happy is he going to be?
那他准备要多快乐
Will he whistle while he works,
他是会在工作的时候吹口哨呢
Or will he just skip around the house occasionally?
还是说他会围着房子欢快的跳
I did not raise you to be bitchy.
我可没教过你说话这么恶毒
No, you raised me to be passive-aggressive.
是  你没教  你教我当笑面虎
My bitchiness-- that was self-taught.
毒舌  这是我自学的
Well, save it for those karaoke parties at Bob and Lee's.
留着到鲍勃和李的卡拉OK聚会上说吧
I am not amused.
我可不觉得有趣
Mom, your b.s. meter might be broken,
妈  你心智被蒙蔽了
But mine works just fine.
但是我很清醒
Orson's up to something.
奥森在搞什么鬼
Well, I can understand why you're a bit cynical,
我可以理解你为什么有点刻薄
But I'm giving him another chance.
但我要再给他一次机会
He's my husband, and i still love him.
他是我丈夫  我还爱他
He's been stealing stuff from your friends.
他从你朋友那里偷东西
He tried to get you to sell your business.
他还想让你卖掉你的公司
I know.
我知道
Fine.
好
Go ahead. Take him back.
去吧  把他接回来吧
But while you're watching orson skip and sing,
但如果你发现奥森又跳又唱
I'll be looking up divorce lawyers, just in case.
我就去找离婚律师  以防万一
Susan, you here?
苏珊  你在吗
In the kitchen.
我在厨房
Why are you mopping the ceiling?
你干嘛刷房顶
I was cooking, all right?
我在做饭
Lids.
锅盖
Susan, you really gotta start using lids.
苏珊  你真的要开始用锅盖了
Sometimes it's the stove's fault.
有时候是炉子的问题
So i, uh, saw dave last night.
我昨晚去看大卫了
How'd that go?
怎么样
Not good. he's in a really dark place.
很不好  他情绪很低落
He kinda lashed out at me.
他对我发脾气
At you? why?
对你  为什么
I don't know. it's like all of a sudden,
我不知道  很突然
He resents my happiness with katherine.
他憎恨我和凯瑟琳的感情
-That's weird.
-太奇怪了
maybe not. when your wife dies,
可能也不奇怪  尤其当妻子去世了
It must be depressing
看到其他人有自己的爱人
To see other people in a loving relationship.
一定很受打击
Hey, maybe you could look in on him.
或许你该去看看他
Yeah, yeah, That didn't come out right.
是  不该这么说
I know what you meant.
我知道你意思
I'll stop by tomorrow and see him.
我明天会去看他
Thanks.
谢啦
You know, this whole thing with edie...
伊迪的事情
I mean, seeing her lying in the street that night...
看到她那晚在街上躺着
Oh, it just brought up
唤醒我所有可怕的回忆
All those awful memories from our accident.
让我回想起咱们那次事故
Susan.
苏珊
We did what we had to do.
我们已经做了我们该做的
Yeah.
是
Look what it did to us.
想想那次事故害得我们...
Daddy!
爸爸
buddy.
宝贝
Hey, you hungry?
你饿了吗
No. Mommy made spaghetti.
不饿  妈妈做了意大利面
All right, I'll, uh, O'll have him back before school.
好  上学之前我会带他回来
You take care.
你自己保重
You, too.
你也是
I'm on my way to work,
我现在要去工作
But I just wanted to bring you these.
但是我想给你带点东西
Uh, chicken salad sandwiches, which I did not make.
鸡肉沙拉三明治  不是我做的
I bought. i learned my lesson from the casserole.
我买的  已经在做砂锅炖菜中得到教训了
Uh, thanks.
谢谢
Uh, wait.
等等
Could you maybe have one right now
你现在可能想吃一个
So that i know that you ate something?
这样我就知道你确实吃东西了
I'm not hungry, but again, thanks.
我不饿  还是谢谢你
Dave, i know that you're going through hell,
大卫  我知道你现在很痛苦
But edie was my friend, so please, let me help you.
但是伊迪是我的朋友  让我来帮帮你
Just a little.
就帮点小忙
You sure you don't want one? it's really good.
你确定你不想要尝尝吗  还不错
Still not hungry.
我还是不饿
So... have you thought about what you're gonna do now?
你有没有想过你要做什么
I'm gonna sell the house.
我要把这房子卖了
You're kidding. so soon?
你开玩笑吧  这么快
I've got a realtor coming by today.
今天会有个房地产中介来找我
I'm gonna put the money in a trust for travers.
我会把这笔钱给特拉法斯存起来
It's, uh, it's what edie would have wanted.
伊迪想这么做
Okay, well...
好
At least you're making plans for the future.
至少你是为未来做些打算
Everything that ever mattered to me is gone.
我曾关心的一切都不在了
The future's the last thing i'm thinking about.
我才不会去想未来
Uh, well, I should Probably... put these away
我想  我应该把这些收起来
Before I finish them off.
要不然我都吃光了
Are you sure there's nothing I can do to help you?
你确定没什么我可以帮忙的吗
A load of laundry?
洗衣服吗
No, thanks.
不用  谢谢
How about a pot of coffee?
要不要来喝点咖啡
Or I could just...
或者我可以
Straighten up in here?
把这里清理一下
Susan, please. I need to be alone.
求你了  苏珊  我想要一个人呆着
okay.
好
Sure.
Do you know what is a great cure for the blues? cribbage
你知道治疗郁闷的良药是什么吗  纸牌
do you have a cribbage set?
你有纸牌吗
I thought you had to go to work
我想你该去上班了
I'll call in sick, take the day off.
我可以打电话  抱病请假一天
Susan...
苏珊
I really don't want to be rude, but you need to leave.
我真的不想无礼  但是你该走了
Okay.
好
You have a realtor coming, right?
一会儿房屋中介会来  是吗
You cannot let him see the house in this condition.
你不想让他看到你的房子这么乱吧
So just let me clean up a little.
让我帮你稍微打扫一下
You won't even know I'm here.
我马上就走
All right.
好吧
I will be back after work to check on you.
我下班再来看你
But until then,
但是  在那之前
Here's the phone, in case you wanna order chinese
给你电话  如果你想点个中国菜
Or...
或者
Call a hotline or something.
打给热线电话
Hey, katherine, can you call me back as soon as you can?
你好  凯瑟琳  听到的话  给我回电话
I just left dave, and he's in bad shape.
我刚刚离开大卫家  他非常不好
I actually think that he might be--
我真的觉得他可能会
Oh, crap. I gotta go.
该死  我先挂了
-Yes, officer?
-你好  长官
License and registration, please.
请拿出驾驶执照
Oh, okay. uh, what did I do?
好  我做什么了
It's again the law to talk on a cell phone
驾驶时  讲电话没用免提装置
Without using a hands-free device while driving,
这是违法的
As of january 1st.
从1月1日起
Right. I know that. I just was worried about a friend,
好  我知道这个  我只是在关心一个朋友
So I forgot. I'm sorry.
所以我忘了  抱歉
Step out of the car slowly.
慢慢走下车来
- Uh, what? you don't want the license?
-什么  你不看驾照了吗
Out of the car.
下车
You think that I'm dangerous.
你以为我是歹徒吗
- No, I totally have an explanation for those.
-不  我要跟你解释一下
Stop talking.
住嘴
You're gonna feel really silly when you
如果你知道这是什么
- Hear what it is.
-你就会觉得我很傻了
Get off the car
下车
Okay.
好
- On the ground!
-趴到地上
oh, yes, Sir!
是的  长官
Hey, susan. i just got your message about dave.
你好  苏珊  我刚听到你的留言
I'm on my way to the hospital, but if you want me to, I...
我正在去医院的路上  如果你想让我  我
You know, why don't we talk later?
我想还是待会再说吧
Hey, tom.
嘿  汤姆
Was that patty rizzo?
那是帕蒂.瑞索吗?
Yeah. i had some car trouble, so she followed me
是的  我的车出了点故障
Over to the garage and gave me a lift back.
她开车陪我去车行  顺便载我回来
Patty lives six blocks away. i live down the street.
她家离这儿有六街区  而我住这么近
Why didn't you ask me to take you?
为什么不叫我载你呢?
Are you going somewhere with this?
你到底想说什么?
All right, look, tom, i'm sorry,
好了  汤姆  我很抱歉
but i got a responsibility here
但我得负责
I brought you into the club.
是我介绍你去俱乐部的
I introduced you to the horny homemaker.
是我把你介绍给那个淫荡的女人的
- I just don't want you to...
-我只是不想让你...
what, gaby, cheat on my wife?
加布  你是说背叛我老婆?
I was gonna say "die of gonorrhea,"
我刚刚想说"死于淋病"
But that's close enough.
但都差不多
Okay, um, i really appreciate your concern,
好的  我很感谢你的关心
But how can i put this?
该说些什么呢?
Butt out.
离我远点
All right, tom, you leave me no choice.
好的  汤姆  是你逼我这么做的
You are no longer allowed to see patty.
不准你再见帕蒂了
"allowed"? who are you, my mother?
"不准?"  你以为你是谁?  我妈妈?
I trump your mother. i am garden club president.
我有权这么做  因为我是园艺俱乐部的主席
This is ridiculous.
太可笑了
- I thought you were my friend.
-我以为我们是朋友
Look, i love you, tom,
汤姆  我喜欢你
But you're my friend with a small "f."
但我们的关系只是说得过去
My friend with the big "f" is lynette.
勒奈特是我的朋友
So if i see something that could hurt her,
如果我发现你伤害她
You bet your ass i'm gonna do something about it.
我可是要动真格的
a neighbor offers me a ride
我搭了下邻居的顺风车
If you want to hurt lynette
如果你将事情无中生有
And twist it into something that it isn't, screw you.
伤害到了勒奈特  那滚蛋
And that's with a big "f."
那才是"朋友"啊
Hello, my love.
嗨  亲爱的
Oh, hello, darling. please tell me you're here to spring me.
亲爱的  告诉我  是你带来了新鲜空气
Not that i haven't enjoyed every moment
不是说我不喜欢
Of your poking and prodding.
你对我戳戳点点的
I'm just taking one last loo
我只是想再给他做一次检查
Are you sure he wasn't in some sort of bar fight?
你确定这些伤不是在酒吧打架造成的吗
It looks like he got smacked over the head
他的头上有撞伤的痕迹
With a pool cue or something.
用撞球球杆还是类似的东西造成的
orson's not exactly
奥森可不是会打架的人
He's more of a raised-voices- at-a-cheese-tasting
他顶多只会拉大嗓门
type. while i'm finish up here
好了  差不多了
Do you wanna go sign the discharge papers?
你现在方便办出院手续吗?
Great. be back in a minute.
太好了  一会就回来
Bree?
布里?
Katherine. hi. what are you doing here?
凯瑟琳  你在这干嘛
Oh, i came to see rose kemper.
我来看看瑞斯·凯普
Oh, right. i heard she was here.
对了  我听说她也住院了
Yeah, it's so sad. i'm here to help her pack.
对  她挺可怜的  我来帮她收拾一下
Social services is coming this afternoon
社工下午来医院
- To take her to some nursing home.
-带她去什么私立疗养院
I'm surprised.
真的吗?
i knew she was a bit dotty
我知道她有点神经兮兮的
But didn't think it was that serious.
但不知道有那么严重
yes. she's been telling people this story
她不停告诉人们
About how death broke into her house.
死神如何闯进她家
Death?
死神?
Oh, dear.
天哪
Apparently he climbed in through a window
显然死神爬进她的窗户
And then tried to steal one of her knickknacks.
试图偷走她的小装饰物
Well, that's odd.
太荒谬了
Yeah. then she whacked him across the head
然后她奋力用她的棒球棒
With a baseball bat.
向死神脑袋打去
A bat?
球棒?
Which is what i would do
如果死神来偷我的小东西
If death were ever to steal one of my knickknacks.
我也会这么做
So did she get a good look at... death?
那她一定看清楚死神长什么样了
No. she said he was wearing some sort of mask.
没有  她说死神带了个面具之类的东西
She tells the story so convincingly,
她信誓旦旦的样子
You almost believe her.
说得像真的一样
Oh, there's the social worker.
社工来了
I wanna be there when she talks to rose.
我得过去了
He's all yours, bree.
布里  把老公还给你了
Wonderful.
太好了
this dinner is delicious.
晚餐棒极了
You really didn't have to do this.
你太客气了
with the long hours you've been putting in
我只是想
I just wanted to do something special to
做点有意义的事情
- say thank you.
-来表示我的感谢
and by "do something"
说到"做点什么"
He means having me slave over a rack of lamb all day.
他是说让我辛辛苦苦烤了一天的羊排
I would like to propose a toast.
我们来干一杯
Who says that friendship and business don't mix?
谁说友谊和生意不能有交集
- To friendship.
-为友谊干杯
hear, hear. to friendship.
为我们的友谊
So i want to hear more about the garden club.
讲讲你们园艺俱乐部有趣的事吧
Tom says he's meeting all kinds of nice people.
汤姆说他认识了很多不错的朋友
Really?
真的吗
Any favorites, tom?
你最喜欢哪个
They're all great gals.
她们都很不错
One's sort of a pain in the ass.
除了有一个很难搞
Other than her, i'm having a great time.
除了她  其他都很不错
I keep telling tom how dangerous gardens can be.
我一直告诉汤姆园艺也是很危险的
Everywhere you step,
你可能会踩到铁铲
There are shovels and rakes and hoes.
耙子  或是锄头
You know, lynette and i should really be toasting you two.
勒奈特和我应该敬你们一杯
Mm. us?
我们
Yeah, for putting up
对啊
With all the long hours we've been keeping.
为包容我们长时间在外工作
Hey, i didn't mind the long hours.
时间长短倒没什么
I wasn't so crazy about the whole shower thing,
只是关于那次淋浴...
but... oh, so lynette told you about that?
勒奈特都给你说了
Yeah, she thought i was nuts for getting weird about it.
她觉得我那是无理取闹
I get it.
我明白
A guy carries your unconscious, naked wife to your bed...
一个男人背着你无意识全裸的妻子到你们的床上...
What are you talking about?
你在说什么
Hey, is this gorgonzola?
这是戈尔贡佐拉羊奶酪吗
The other day when she fell in your shower.
有天她在洗澡时滑倒了
What are you talking about?
你又在说什么
when she took a shower in you office
是在你的办公室洗澡
-You took a shower in my office?
-你在我办公室洗澡
What's going on here?
到底是怎么回事?
Lynette was taking a shower
那天卡洛斯顺道载勒奈特去工作
And carlos came by to drive her to work.
勒奈特正在洗澡
She slipped and fell, and he helped her.
她滑倒了  他就帮了她
you told her? i asked you not to
你告诉她了  我让你别说的
She's my wife. i tell her everything
她是我老婆  我什么都给她说
oh, you hear that, lynette? they tell each other everything
听见了吗  勒奈特  他们什么都开诚布公
That way they know that they're not hiding anything.
他们都知道夫妻间不该有秘密
i was just afraid Like you're doing... right now.
我只是怕你像现在这样反应过度
full disclosure, lynette--that's what a marriage is about
透露下  这就是我们的婚姻
So i assume you fully disclosed you
那我可以透露下
fully disclosed Your little "friendship" with patty rizzo.
你和帕蒂.瑞索之间的"友谊"吗
What little friendship?
怎么回事
You know what? i think this is gorgonzola.
我觉得这就是戈尔贡佐拉羊奶酪
Tom?
汤姆
Well, patty gave me a ride home,
只是帕蒂有天载我回家
And for some reason, gaby's making a big deal about it.
不知道为什么加布老是揪着我不放
Because it's patty rizzo. she's a total slut.
因为那是帕蒂.瑞索  她是个荡妇
You should be on antibiotics just for sitting in her car.
你坐她的车都应该打一剂抗生素的
Exactly.
完全正确
Stay out of this, gaby. you've done enough damage.
加布  够了  你把这搞得够乱了
Hey, don't snap at me. lynette's my friend.
别教训我  勒奈特是我的朋友
I was just watching her back.
我只是在保护她
while your husband was watching her front.
是啊  你丈夫只是在饱眼福
Drop it, tom.
够了  汤姆
We'll continue this at home.
我们回家再讨论
If you have a shower at the office,
如果你的办公室有淋浴
How come you come home smelling so bad?
为什么你回到家还臭烘烘的
I don't know.
我不知道
Why does the lamb taste like sawdust?
但为什么羊排吃起来像锯屑
Oh, thank you, darling.
谢谢  亲爱的
I can't tell you how nice it is to be home again.
回到家的感觉真好
Well, it's wonderful to have you home.
有你在家感觉真好
How's your head?
感觉好些了吗
Mm, it still hurts.
还是有点疼
Well, that'll teach you
这是给你的教训
To go out walking in the middle of the night.
让你知道半夜出去散步的下场
You know, i still don't know why you were out so late.
我还是不明白你那么晚出去干嘛
Well, i told you.
我给你说过了
We had a little spat, and i wanted to clear my head.
我们吵架后  我想冷静一下
Oh. and then you bumped it on that nasty curb.
然后就撞到了路边的井拦
Well, that'll teach me to fight with my lovely wife.
这告诉我和我可爱老婆吵架没有好处
And that's all you were doing,
你就只是出去
Just going out for a walk?
走了一下
That's all.
对
Oh, you know, i just remembered
哦  我想起来生意上有些事
Some business i have to discuss with andrew.
还得和安德鲁商量一下
Enjoy your tea.
慢慢喝
Hey, mom. what's wrong?
妈妈  怎么了
Orson's lying to me again.
奥森又对我撒谎了
So i think i have to divorce him.
我想我得和他离婚了
Just, uh, tell me how i can help.
说说我该怎么帮你
You okay?
你还好吧
I just keep thinking about dave.
我只是在想大卫
His life was so great. he had everything.
他曾拥有美好的生活
Then one day, boom! all gone.
然后  嘣  什么都没有了
Yeah, i know.
我能理解
Life can turn on a dime--
生活总是不断在变
Dave, Edie, Rose Kemper
大卫  伊迪  瑞斯·凯普
The one thing it's made me realize is...
这些事让我越发觉得
I don't want to live with regrets.
我不想在忏悔中生活
Me neither.
我也是
I've been wanting to tell you this for some time.
我一直都想告诉你
Remember when i suggested moving in together?
记得我提议搬在一起住吗
It wasn't just about saving rent.
不只是为了减少开支
I was trying to pull you closer,
我原本想抓紧你
Manipulate some kind of commitment out of you.
想从你那里得到些许诺
that's not who i am, so i want you to know that i'm sorry
那不是真正的我  我想让你知道我很抱歉
And it won't happen again.
再也不会发生了
From now on, no hidden agendas.
从现在起  没有秘密
I like that policy.
我喜欢这项提议
I'm always gonna be honest with you.
我会一直坦诚相待
After all,
毕竟
You're the guy i'm gonna spend the rest of my life with.
我们将共度余生
Ah, more sandwiches.
你给我带了三明治
Or is my gun in there?
还是我的枪
It's just your belts and ties.
只是你的皮带和领带
The police kept the rest.
警察把其余的都没收了
I know. they called.
我知道  他们通知我了
You told them i was suicidal.
你告诉他们我打算自杀
I'm sorry.
对不起
It's just-- the things you said...
只是你说那些话
I'm worried about you.
让我很担心
Don't be.
别
I told you, i'm fine.
我告诉过你  我很好
You are not fine.
你不好
How could you be?
你怎么会很好?
You have suffered a horrible loss.
你经历了一场噩梦
And you are allowed to feel any way you want.
你有任何感受都不为过
But i know that you are not fine.
但我知道你过着多糟的生活
Okay, well, i'm sorry for ransacking your house.
好了  抱歉在你家翻来翻去
I'll stop bugging you.
不打扰你了
Edie and i had a fight...
那晚  伊迪和我
That night.
吵了一架...
A bad one.
吵得很厉害
I came home.
我回到家
We argued.
我们就争吵着
She stormed out, got in her car and died.
后来她冲出去  开着车  然后就死了
Oh, dave...
大卫...
That does not make it your fault.
这不是你的错
Doesn't it?
不是吗
If things had been different, if i...
如果事情不是那样  如果我...
Had been different, she'd still be alive.
不那么做  她就不会死
You can't think that way.
你不能这么去想
what happened is bad enough.
发生的事情已经够糟了
you can't blame yourself for it, too.
你不能再自责
If you do that,
如果你这么做
You will destroy everything you have left that's good.
你会把你拥有一切美好的事都毁掉
Trust me. i know.
相信我  我知道你的感受
Trust me. you don't.
相信我  你不知道
A few years ago, mike and i got in a car accident.
几年前  麦克和我经历过一场车祸
A woman and her daughter... died.
一个女人和她的女儿丧生了
Yeah, i-i heard about that.
我听说过
Mike was driving, right?
麦克开的车  对吧
That's what we said...
我们这样对大家说的
But it wasn't true.
但并不是真的
After the crash,
撞车后
I couldn't find my license.
我找不到我的驾照
I had switched purses that night,
那晚我换了包
And i had left it at home, and so...
忘记了拿驾照  所以
Mike... told them that he was driving.
麦克告诉他们是他开的车
He took the blame for me.
他帮我顶了罪
So...
所以...
I understand guilt.
我深知内疚的感受
And i want you to understand
我想让你明白
That edie's death was an awful tragedy.
伊迪的死完全是一场事故
It was not your fault.
不是你的错
Maybe you're right.
或许你是对的
Thank you for telling me.
谢谢你告诉我这些
Heck of a dinner party, huh?
一顿糟糕的晚餐
It's amazing how fast you can eat in total silence.
我很惊讶  你不说话可以吃得那么快
It's my fault. i should have just told tom the truth,
我的过错  我应该告诉汤姆事情的真相
Although it turned out to be kind of a wash
这样就和帕蒂.瑞索那件事
With the whole patty rizzo thing.
扯平了
You know what i think is cool?
其实这很棒
You guys have been married a long time,
我是说结婚这么多年
And you still get jealous.
却还有激情吃彼此的醋
Yeah. but just to be on the safe side,
也对  但安全起见
If i fall in my tub again, let me die there.
下次如果我滑到了  让我横尸浴室
Okay. back to work.
好的  回去工作了
Yes. and we shall never speak this again.
我们再也别提这件事了
I am embarrassed enough.
有够丢脸的了
Lynette?
勒奈特
I saw you without your towel.
我连你裸体都见了
You got nothing to be embarrassed about.
还有什么好丢脸的
How's the garden club today?
今天在园丁俱乐部怎么样
Oh, phyllis got tanked on cosmos
菲里丝把波斯菊放到了水槽里
and threw up on edna...
然后扔向爱德娜
So now we're back to planting crap.
我们现在又开始准备对决了
Look, i'm really sorry for sticking my nose
我真的很抱歉
Into that whole patty rizzo thing.
对聚会上的事太敏感
It's okay. i...
没关系  我
The truth is, is i knew she was coming on to me.
事实是  我知道她直接奔我来的
Then why did you keep hanging out with her?
那你为什么还跟她一起出去
Lynette has been so swamped with work lately,
勒奈特最近忙着工作
That she doesn't...
她不
It's just nice having a woman notice me again.
只是又有女人注意我  这感觉很好
Is that terrible?
我是不是很烂
No. i get it.
不  我能理解
When we first moved here,
我们刚搬到这里的时候
Carlos was working round the clock,
卡洛斯没日没夜地工作
And he'd chome and barely say hello to me.
他回到家甚至招呼都懒得跟我打
It was like i was invisible.
就像我是透明的
Invisible-- that's the word.
透明的  就是这个词了
So when he didn't see me, i found someone who did.
所以当他不见我时  我就找人见我
Y-you know i'd never do that to lynette.
我从没对勒奈特做过这种事
I never thought i'd do it to carlos.
我也从没想过会对卡洛斯做这种事
Then it's a good thing
这是件好事
I've got a friend around to keep an eye on me,
有朋友监督我
Even if it's one with a small "f."
虽然我没勒奈特对你那么贴心
Well, for the record, you're growing on me.
正式声明  我要开始监督了
You know what? i'm thirsty.
我有些渴了
Let's start a book club.
我们去书友俱乐部看看
The fact is everyone does it.
人人都会掩饰
Everyone tries to cover up what
人人都在试图掩饰
they don't want others to see
不想让别人看到的东西
Women hide their need for commitment...
女人掩饰她们想要的承诺
Men disguise their growing insecurity...
男人掩饰他们日益增加的不安全感
Wives mask their intense disdain.
妻子掩饰她们深深的蔑视
How can ordinary people
常人怎能
Hide the truth of their feelings so successfully?
如此成功地掩饰他们的感觉
All it takes is a friendly gesture...
示好是必须的  友好在先
You can't play in the street, m.j.
MJ  你不能在大街上踢球
You could get hurt,
你会被伤着的
And that would really tear your mom apart.
你妈妈要伤心死的
And a plan.
谋划在后